let questions1 = [
    {
       numb: 1,
       question: "Employees have access to data, equipment, and the network.",
       answer: "C. Internal",
       options: [
        "A. External",
        "B. Unstructured",
        "C. Internal",
        "D. Structured"
       ]
    },

    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "This program can produce like a virus and spread to other computers?",
        answer: "C. Trojan",
        options:
        [
           "A. Virus",
           "B. Worm",
           "C. Trojan",
           "D. External"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Is a self-replicating program that is harmful to networks?",
        answer: "B. Worm",
        options:
        [
           "A. Virus",
           "B. Worm",
           "C. Trojan",
           "D. external"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Is a program written with malicious intent and sent out by attackers?",
        answer: "A. Virus",
        options:
        [
            "A. Virus",
           "B. Worm",
           "C. Trojan",
           "D. External"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "A technology created by Microsoft to control interactivity on web pages?",
        answer: "D. ActiveX",
        options:
        [
            "A. Java",
            "B. HTML",
            "C. JavaScript",
            "D. ActiveX"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "A programming language that allows applets to run within a web browser?",
        answer: "A. Java",
        options:
        [
            "A. Java",
           "B. HTML",
           "C. JavaScript",
           "D. ActiveX"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Sends abnormally large amounts of request to a system, preventing access to the services.",
        answer: "B. DoS",
        options:
        [
            "A. DDoS",
            "B. DoS",
            "C. SYN Flood",
            "D. Spoofing"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Is a software program that displays advertising on your computer?",
        answer: "C. Adware",
        options:
        [
            "A. Grayware",
           "B. Spyware",
           "C. Adware",
           "D. DoS"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Is the protocol suite that is used to control all of the communications on the internet?",
        answer: "D. TCI/IP",
        options:
        [
            "A. DNS Poisoning",
           "B. DoS",
           "C. Man-in-the-Middle",
           "D. TCI/IP"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What does WPA stand for?",
        answer: "A. Wi-Fi Protected Access",
        options:
        [
          "A. Wi-Fi Protected Access",
          "B. Wired Protected Access",
          "C. Wireless Protocol Access",
          "D. wi-Fi Protocol Access"
        ]
    }
    
];